gstseva.com 2017-06-08

# PRIVACY POLICY | GST-Seva | GST in India | GST news | GST updates | GST consultants | GST bill

GSTSEVA.COM does not collect any personal information about individuals except when such individuals specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis. Personal information on individual users will not be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties.

GSTSEVA.COM reserves the right to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the site and to inform advertisers of such information as well as the number of users that have been exposed to or clicked on their advertising banners. GSTSEEVA.COM will provide only aggregated data from these analyses to third parties.

Users are also being aware that non-personal information and data may be automatically collected through the standard operation of GSTSEVA.COM internet servers or through the use of “cookies.” “Cookies” are small text files a web site can use to recognize repeat users, facilitate the user’s ongoing access to and use of the site and allow a site to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements and targeted advertising.

Cookies are not programs that come onto a user’s system and damage files. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the user that has no meaning outside the assigning site. Users are also being made aware that GSTSEVA.COM cannot control the use of cookies or the resulting information by advertisers or third parties hosting data for GSTSEVA.COM If a user does not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the user to deny or accept the cookie feature; however, users should note that cookies may be necessary to provide the user with certain features like customized delivery of information as and when made available by GSTSEVA.COM.

GSTSEVA.COM reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying users of the existence of a new privacy statement. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
